[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Maryland Day is celebrated every year on what date?", "correct_answer": "March 25th", "incorrect_answers": ["The first day of crab season", "Preakness Saturday", "March 1st"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a drinking game played with 1 oz shots of beer and cards. The player must guess the rank that was dealt to another players card. At the end, one of the players has to drink many beer shots.", "correct_answer": "Hi-Lo", "incorrect_answers": ["Bortok", "FizzBuzz", "Bizu-Bizu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When the producers of the movie Snakes on a Plane wanted to change the title, actor Samuel L. Jackson protested, saying the only reason he took the job was because of the title.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What book did Sleepers character Shakes love the most?", "correct_answer": "The Count of Monte Cristo", "incorrect_answers": ["The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", "Moby Dick", "Oliver Twist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the religion of Sikhism, it is every Sikhs duty to defeat what five vices?", "correct_answer": "Ego, anger, greed, attachment, and lust", "incorrect_answers": ["Religious zealots, political zealots, money lending, sexual allurement and gluttony", "Alcohol, pork, money, gold, and diamonds", "Drunkenness, lewdness, murder, rape and theft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The setting is a campfire. Gathered around are Captain America, Billy, and the lawyer, George Hanson.  The lawyer looks around and says, Nic-nic-nic. What cult movie are you watching?", "correct_answer": "Easy Rider", "incorrect_answers": ["Five Easy Pieces", "Reefer Madness", "The Day the World Stood Still"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the biggest Greek island ?", "correct_answer": "Crete", "incorrect_answers": ["Rhodes", "Cyprus", "Euboea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Little Miss Sunshine, who played the mom, Sheryl?", "correct_answer": "Toni Collette", "incorrect_answers": ["Lauren Graham", "Blythe Danner", "Sheryl Fenn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This director, who has played drums for Kanye West, directed The  Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind, Human Nature and Be Kind Rewind.", "correct_answer": "Michael Gondry", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Siegel", "Gore Verbinski", "Tim Burton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The catch phrase, The Truth Is Out There originated from which of these popular television series, dealing with mysteries and extraterrestrial life?", "correct_answer": "The X-Files", "incorrect_answers": ["The First Wave", "The Twilight Zone", "The Outer Limits"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All aquatic turtles have flippers instead of feet.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of disturbance can pine nuts cause in about 1 to 3 days following their consumption?", "correct_answer": "Unusual taste in the mouth", "incorrect_answers": ["Fever and vomiting", "Migraine", "Partial blindness"]}]